A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 9
  - Properties, 9.2
    - Hotel at Brenas Beach, Puerto Rico: Ground Floor & First Floor Plumbing Plans, 1969, 1971; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 2)
    - Site Plan Showing locations of Exterior Lights, Brenas Beach Hotel, 1971 September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 2)
    - 8 topographic maps of golf course with different hand-colored and labeled areas, Dorado Beach, 1968 April, 1969 September; MAP (Quantity 8) (Drawer E 5, Folder 2)
    - Hotel at Brenas Beach, Dorado, Puerto Rico: Ground Floor and 1st Floor Plan (Drawings A4 & A5), with notes written in pencil, 1969 November 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 2)
    - topographic maps on mylar "Parcel of Land Property of LSR... Vega Alta, Puerto Rico", 1969 June; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 5, Folder 2)
    - Caneel Bay Plantation: Location Plan, St. John's V.I., Cruz Bay Bulkhead, 1956 November 7; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1); small (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on back "Cruz Bay Dock-N.O. Wells-11/7/56"
    - Boat Yard Area, Caneel Bay Plantation, Cruz Bay, St. John's V.I., 1962 June 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "N.O. Wells survey-Cruz Bay-8/1/62"
    - 2 photocopied schematics "Proposed Perimeter Control Gate", 1963 January 4; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Gate at Sugar Mill Ruins-Caneel-1/11/63"
    - Revised Alterations & Editions for Building F-8 for Stand-By Power Plant" marked in pencil "Dec. 14", 1956 October 15; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Existing Generator Plant-Caneel-1/4/63"
    - 1 elevation "Suggested Layout, Alterations & Expansion, Caneel Bay Main Kitchen, St. John's V.I." with penciled notes and shading, 1963 March 26; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Caneel Kit. Alt.-3/26/63"
    - Distribution Transformer Rearrangement Plan, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1960 July 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      labeled on back "Project 22A-Changes to Electrical Distribution System-Caneel Bay"
    - Suggested Layout, Kitchen & Bar Area; Alterations to Turtle Bay House, Caneel Bay Plantation, St. John's V.I., 1961 January 31; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Turtle Bay Kit."
    - Master Map of Estate, Caneel Bay; #8 Cruz Bay Quarter, St. Johns V.I., 1964 April 10; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - Caneel Bay Plantation: Drawing S-2 & E-2, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on back "Nat Wells-Dam Vol-Caneel"
    - Tennis Court Shelter, 1966 October 3; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on back "1 print to Toro-4/13/67-PKN-Alternate Design-Tennis Court Shelter-Caneel-10/4/66
    - Proposed Pavilion at Sugar Mill Ruins, Caneel Bay Plantation, Revised: 1969 January 11; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - 2 sets of 5 photocopied blueprints "Alterations-Front Office, Gift Shop, 2nd Floor Lounge-Central Building, Caneel Bay Plantation, St. John's V.I.", 1963 April 1; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 10) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Caneel-Alt Gift Shop etc.-Appvd 6/14/63"
    - Cruz Bay Boat Yard, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1964 June 12; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "P.K.W. revised & final-Boat Yard-Caneel-1/15/65"
    - "Underground Utilities, Lindpoint Residency Area, V.I. National Park (U.S. Department of the Interior), 1963 January; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "V.I. National Park-Underground Elec.- Housing-Cruz Bay 1/1/63"
    - "Gift Shop, Caneel Bay Plantation" with initials & date written in pencil, 1969 May 13; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Food Facilities at Sugar Mill Ruins, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1969 January 23; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - Food Equipment Layout, Sugar Mill Ruins, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1969 June 12. Approved: 1969 July 7; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - Kitchen Alterations, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1969 January 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - 2 sets of 3 "Alterations & Additions to Central Building, Caneel Bay Plantation, St. John V.I."; one set has some notes written in pen, 1957 August 30. Revised: 1957 October 9; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "La Farge-Prints A Roof Plans-Central Building-Caneel"
    - plot map "Cruz Bay Area, Caneel Bay Plantation" w/ handwritten notes & shadings, 1955 November 9; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on back "Plot Map-Caneel Bay Properties-N.O. Wells Survey-Cruz Bay Boat Yard-11/9/55"
    - 2 topographic maps "Walk to Turtle Bay Beach: Proposed and Alternative (drawings 1 and 2), Caneel Bay Plantation;" noted "Approved on 1965 April 14 by LSR", 1962 September 4 and December 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Bryan Lynch-Path to Beach-Turtle Bay-4/8/65"
    - 2 elevation drawings in pencil "Diagram of Linen Storage Space Required (1962 September 4)" "Plan: Existing Laundry Building (1962 September 5)" large photocopied plan "Site Plan of Proposed Linen Storage Site, Caneel Bay Plantation" 1962 August 5., 1962 August-September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Topo Survey-Linen Storage-Caneel-8/14/62"
    - Proposed Linen Storage Site Plan, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1962 August 21; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Bryan Lynch-Site Plan-Linen Storage-Caneel-9/6/62-Topo of site-Condit Sketch of floorplan-Condit floorplan... "
    - "Site Plan-Employees' Village" with notes & drawings in red pencil, 1961 May 9. Revised: 1961 September 25; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side: "Revised-Nature Village-Paving-Caneel-4/26/62"
    - Water Booster System, Caneel Bay Plantation, St. John V.I., 1968 July 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Caneel Bay-Booster Pump-Cosentini 7/31/68"
    - Drawing # 3001-D "General Development-St. John Island-Part of the Master Plan, Virgin Islands National Park"; from the U.S. Dept of the Interior, with hand-painted colors, 1957 May 13; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - "Cruz Bay Development-Part of the Master Plan, Virgin Islands National Park" with charcoal and pencil drawings and watercolor details, 1957 May 10 and 13; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      labeled on back "Natll Park Service: Proposal for Virgin Islands-Master Plan-Caneel Bay"
    - 1 large plan "Master Record Plan, Caneel Bay Plantation Inc, St. John V.I.", 1964 October 26; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - Alterations to Main Kitchen-Food Service Equipment Plan in Detail, 1956 September 1; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on back "Plan-Present Bakery-Caneel"
    - First Floor Plan: Additions to Commissary, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1953 September 28. Revised: 1955 May 3; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "La Farge-Murphy-Central Building-Caneel-9/28/53"
    - New Building: Cottage #7 Site, Caneel Bay Plantation, St. John V.I., 1962; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 10) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - 2 copies "Drawing #101 Laundry Waste Treatment, Caneel Bay Plantation", 1956 January 26; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
    - 2 sets of 3 "Drawings #1-3 Laundry Building, Mechanical & Electrical, Caneel Bay Plantation", 1955 December-1956 January; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Laundry-Project 23-Caneel"
    - New Guest Units, Caneel Bay, St. John V.I., 1963 April 1; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 11) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "La Farge & Murphy-Project 118-Caneel-4 Room Guest Units-4/1/63" and "Print of Drawing #3-Floorplan of Elevation sent to Toro/Ferrer on 5/4/66 HB"
    - 2 copies "Project 114: 1962 Program-Road and Path Lighting, Caneel Bay Plantation, St. John V.I.", 1963 October 28; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Path Lighting-Caneel-5/1/64"
    - Manager's Cottage, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1961 October 2; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "... Ground Floor-Manager's Cottage-Caneel- 5/1/64"
    - Alterations to the "Little House", Caneel Bay Plantation, 1963 January 2; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Revised-Little House-Caneel-7/1/63"
    - Alterations: Dining Terrace, Coffee Service, Buffet; Caneel Bay Plantation", 1961 October 17; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on side "Screen-Dining Terrace-Caneel-7/30/62"
    - 2 photocopies of blueprints "New Entrances to Existing 12-Room Beachfront Units, Caneel Bay Plantation", 1960 January 31. revised: 1960 June 27; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      labeled on back "Caneel: Rear Entrances-Old Beach front Units-7/7/60 #82 2/9/60"
    - Sheets 1-4 Project No.206, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1969 March 31; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 5, Folder 3)
      marked on back "CBP-Proj 206-Sugar Mill"
    - Roads, Water and Sewarage Systems, Virgin Islands National Park-Preliminary Drawings, marked in pen 1970 March 16., 1970 February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 12) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
      marked on back "CBP 264 CINN BAY NPS Drawings 3/16/70"
    - 1 unmarked plan, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - 1 untitled plan (Schiff-Condit Architecture & Site Planners), WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - 2 colored drawings with glued labels "Four-Unit Beach Cottages, Cinnamon Bay, V.I. National Park", with 2 blueline copies, 1969 August; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
      marked on back "Cinn Bay Cottages"
    - Camping Facilities-Cinnamon Bay, V. I., WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
      marked on back "Cinn Bay Wash Facilities"
    - Cinnamon Bay Camping Cottages, Caneel Bay Plantation, V.I., 1970 May 12-13; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 13) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Cinnamon Bay Camping Cottages, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 8) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Camping Facilities-Cinnamon Bay, St. John V.I., 1970 February 2; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 7) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Cinnamon Bay-For Budget Only, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 8) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Camping Facilities-Cinnamon Bay, US V.I., ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - revised electrical & mechanical drawings "Camping Facilities-Cinnamon Bay, St. John V.I.", with 2 copies of mechanical drawings, 1970 February 2. Revised: 1970 February 18 and April 8; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 9) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Central Facilities Schedules, Camping Facilities, Cinnamon Bay St. John V.I., 1970 May 12; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 10) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - 2 copies "Master Site Plan, Camping Facilities, Cinnamon Bay, V.I.", one with notes, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Final Food Facilities Plan, Cinnmon Bay, V.I. National Park, 1969 December. Revised: 1970 January 12; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Camping Facilities-Cinnamon Bay, St. John V.I., 1970 February 2. Revised: 1970 February 18; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - 3 blueline drawings from Camping Facilities, Cinnamon Bay, St. John V.I. (untitled but matching to previous titles), 1970 January 30; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 6, Folder 1)
    - Revisions to Roads, Water and Sewerage Systems, Cinnamon Bay V.I., 1969 November. Received: 1969 December 29; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 1 untitled blueline drawing marked "C.B.C.F.3" (Schiff-Condit Architects), WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - Main Beach Station Study, Cinnamon Bay, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 4 untitled plans from Cinnamon Bay Camping Facilities, labeled with permanent marker, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - Base Sheet-Cinnamon Bay-Service Building, V.I., 1969 October 25 and November 11; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 2 mechanical drawings w/out title box from Cinnamon Bay Camping Facilities, 1970 January 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - set of 5 electrical drawings "Camping Facilities, Cinnamon Bay V.I", 1970 February 2; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 1 topographic survey printed on mylar "Little Dix Bay Development Property Survey", 1963 June 26; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 2 topographic surveys printed on mylar "Topographic map of a Section of Dorado Beach Hotel Farm, Dorado, Puerto Rico", MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - surveys and elevation drawings with hand-coloring and notes "Caneel Bay Staff Housing, Cruz Bay, U.S.V.I.", 1970 April 29; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 16) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 2 sets of 3 photocopied plans, some with drawings "Cruz Bay Housing", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - Site Plan, Caneel Bay Staff Housing Dwg. 1, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 1 blueline plan "Parcel 12 Remainder, Estate: Caneel Bay", 1969 December 8; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - drawn with marker "C.B.P. Service Area", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
      marked on back "Cruz Bay-St.John, Site Plan & Service Area"
    - 1 drawing with colored marker "Site Plan-NPS-C.B.P. Area-Cruz Bay-St. John", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 2 sets of 9 drawings "Schedules: Caneel Bay Staff Housing, Cruz Bay, St. John U.S.V.I.", 1970 May 12. Revised: 1970 May 26; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 18) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - Siting Plan-Caneel Bay Staff Housing at Cruz Bay, St. John", 1970 July 26; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - "Caneel Bay Staff Housing Site Plan" with multiple revisions, 1970 May 26-June 16; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 6 drawings with hand-coloring and notes "CRH-C" (Caneel Bay Staff Housing), ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 6 plans "Cruz Bay Housing (Schedules)", 1970 April 24; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 8 blueline prints "Floor Framing-RockResorts, St. John U.S.V.I.", 1970 September; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 8) Oversized: 2. (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 2 blackline prints "CNN:F1" and "CNN:F2", WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 1 "Sewage Treatment Plant, Caneel Bay Staff Housing, Cruz Bay, U.S.V.I.", 1970 November 23; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - 4 elevations "Dorado Beach Hotel-Room Block Details", 1956; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 2)
    - small blueprint "Proposed Relocation of Existing Aluminum Warehouse, Caneel Bay, St. John USVI", noted in pen 1964 March 31, 1964 March 18; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - printed elevation with coloring and labels in pencil "Layout of Existing Kitchen & Bakeshop, Caneel Bay, USVI", 1963 May 5; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
      labeled on back "Condit-As Built Kitchen-Caneel-63"
    - blueprint "Woodstock Country Club Upper, Lower Level" floorplans, 1973 May 18; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Schematic Study-Lower Lobby, Main Floor, Scheme C, Proposed Expansion, Woodstock Inn #134", 1973 March 9; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - 4 "Schematic Study of Proposed Expansion, Lobby, Garden Level, Site Plan, Woodstock Inn", 1973 February 5; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - 3 small survey drawings "Proposed Expansion of Recreation Facilities, Woodstock Country Club (#205) Schemes A & B", 1973 March 3; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Schematic Study of Proposed Expansion, Woodstock Inn, Scheme B", also marked 1973 February 28 in pencil., 1973 February 27; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Sketch-Proposed Improvements, Woodstock Country Club #211" with pencil, 1973 June 17; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Route Plan, Brenas Beach Hotel Golf Course" with written date., 1970 April 1; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - survey drawing "Woodstock Hotel Co. Boundary Survey", 1968 April 5. Revised: 1969 February 17; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - 2 copies of site plan "Woodstock Inn", 1969 January-February; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - set of 4 mechanical elevations "Woodstock Inn, Woodstock VT", with handwritten notes in pencil & marker, 1968 December 12; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - set of 16 sheets in booklet "Woodstock Inn Furniture Layouts", 1969; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 16) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
      labeled on back "Woodstock Furniture Layouts & Rugs-DePolo Assoc-1/69 &7/69, #001"
    - 3 survey drawings "Scheme G, Woodstock Inn, Lobby Level and 2nd Floor", 1967 October 31; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - small photocopy "Exterior Lighting Fixtures Dwg #4383, Woodstock Inn", 1969 August 14; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Building Location Plans, 1967-1968; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Inn, Schemes, 1967 September 12; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 12) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
      labeled on back "Woodstock-Scheme-A-B-C-D-Tabler-1967"
    - "Properties of Woodstock Golf & Tennis Club Associates Inc", with handwritten notes, 1961 May 9; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Furniture Drawings, Woodstock Inn, 1968 October 14; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 17) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - "Site Plans,... Woodstock Inn", 1968 April 25. Revised: 1968 June, July; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 17) (Drawer E 6, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Folklife Museum. 1 sheet Scheme - Lighting Plan Upper Barns; 4 sheets Scheme C - Plans for Mansion (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1981 June 25-26; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 5) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
    - Billings Farm Museum. Building plans. (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1981 August 21; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
    - LSR Property and Related Lands, Woodstock, Vermont. (Northeast Environmental Design (Vermont)), 1973 January; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
    - JY Ranch. Multiples of 3 plats, Tracts D-4, D-5, D-6. Teton County, Wyoming. Includes folder of survey documents., 1980 September 12; MAPS (Quantity 8) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
      D 4-5-6
    - Coastline, Maui, including Seven Sacred Pool and Pryor & Lindbergh properties. (U.S. Geological Survey), 1965 January 21; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
      EKNICC148
    - Additions and Alterations to Residence and Office for Dr. Carol Mitchell-Simmons, St. John, U.S.V.I 00830. With correspondence from Clayton W. Frye. (C. Glover Thompson), 1984 April 13; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
    - 2 copies of: Map of Property prepared for Hills Realty Company, Mt. Pleasant, NY (Chas H. Sells, Inc.), 1972 March; Maps (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
      Marked on back: Rockwood Hall - JDR3 - LSR - IBM
    - JY Ranch. Plats of Tracts B-3, B-D-5, D-2, B-D-1, D-3. Teton County, Wyoming. (Maurice J. Zardus & Christopher L. Albers), 1980 November, 1981 June; MAP (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 9, Folder 1)
    - elevations of "Residence 255 Choke Cherry Drive, Teton County WY" (Peter K. Ogden, CT), 1981 February 28; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 9) (Drawer E 9, Folder 1)
    - survey drawings & elevations for vacation house, St. Bart's (Campbell & Aldrich, Boston MA), 1959--1962; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer E 9, Folder 1)
    - electrical plans, Billings Farm Museum, VT. (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1981 November 20; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 9, Folder 1)
    - colored survey of land plats around Mount Tom, Woodstock VT, 1973; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
    - 3 black & white aerial photographs, 1967 August 3; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 3) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
      1-142, GS-VBRW
    - black & white aerial photograph with map drawn overtop of it, "Aerial View of Parks - Pocantico", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    - Maui, including Seven Sacred Pool and Pryor & Lindbergh properties. (From Tryck, Nyman & Hayes Inc.), 1971 January 23; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
      #30; 72-4
  - Little Dix Bay, 9.3
    - Layout study of the central kitchen., 1966 February 9; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Photocopy: "Layout of Proposed Wind Screen, Project 993-22.", 1964 May 13; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - 2 copies: "Tension Cables?Proposed Fabric Cover Between Administration Building and Dining Pavilion.", 1966 September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Supplemental Potable Water Storage, Project 100., 1964 September 1; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Test Well Location., 1964 July 23; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Modifications: Existing Storm Drainage., 1964 December 10; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - 2 Sewage and Drainage Plans., 1964 July 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Little Dix Bay Hotel: Beach, Kitchen, Floor plan, Pavilion, & Elevations (1 & 2)., 1965; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Little Dix Bay Development, 1961-1964; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 20) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Project 112: Sixteen Room Addition Little Dix Bay, 1968 March 15; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 16) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Masterplan, Little Dix Bay, 1965 May 4; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Drawing on tissue paper: "Centerline elevation", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - "Central Pavilion Area: Elevation towards Southwest" Little Dix Bay, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Plan: Central Pavilion Area, Little Dix Bay, 1965 May 27; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Little Dix Bay Development, 1961-1964; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Topographic Survey: Point Lookout, 1965 March 15; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - 4 Room Guest Unit & 12 Room Guest Unit, Little Dix Bay, 1964 November 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Topography of Little Dix Bay, 1965 April 30; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - 18 Guest Room Wing, Little Dix Bay, 1965 April 30; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - White Print: "Dining Pavilion Supplementary Lighting" Little Dix Bay Development, 1964 June 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - 2 copies of aerial photograph of Little Dix Bay with ink drawing on mylar overlay "Preliminary Site Plan Proposed Modifications", 1969 May 5; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Little Dix Bay "Site & Utilities Plan - Main Building and Floor Plan and Details - Pavilion Area", 1965-1966; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)
    - Proposed Additions and Modifications: Food Service Area and Administration, Little Dix Bay, 1964 November 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1A)